我们所有人中你想下一个结婚的会是谁
Out of all of us, who do you think will get married next?
大概是莫妮卡和钱德
Probably Monica and Chandler.
给我一包新港淡型香烟好吗?
Could I have a pack of Newport Lights?
我们没有卖烟，对街有卖
We don't sell cigarettes, but they do across the street.
那太好了，谢谢
That'd be great. Thanks.
梅莉莎伍伯，我没有力气应付她
Melissa Worbert. I don't think I have the energy for this.
我的天! 瑞瑞格林?
Oh, my God! Ray-Ray Greene?
怎么样?
What's up?!
你是我们社团连续7期周报主角
You've been MIA for seven sorority newsletters.
你怎么样?
What's up with you?
我们到那边去再说?
Why don't I tell you over here?
上次我听说你要结婚了
So last I heard you were gonna get married.
可怜的瑞瑞
Poor Ray-Ray.
不，其实很好
Oh, no. It's all good.
-我现在替罗夫罗兰工作 -闭嘴!
- I actually work at Ralph Lauren.- Shut up!
我不，我是男装运动服饰的分区主管
I will not. I'm the divisional head of mers sportswear.
再闭嘴! 你是拉夫的朋友吗?
Shut up more! Are you friends with Ralph?
拜托 你是吗?
- Oh, please. - Are you?
不是
No.
我们一定要一起吃饭，你明天做什么?
We have to have dinner. What are you doing tomorrow?
-明天，我不知道 -你要和我吃晚饭
- Tomorrow. I don't know.- You're having dinner with me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我要走了，看到你真好
I've gotta go. This has been so great.
哦，这儿，你给我这个真是个坏孩子
Oh, there you are. You're a bad man for giving me these.
-打电话给我，这是我的名片 -哇，谢谢
- So listen, just call me. Here's my card.- Oh, wow, thanks.
-你在做房地产? -不，那是旧名片
- You're in real estate?- No, that's an old card.
我必须离开那工作去做些…
I got out of that to do something...
可以帮助别人和改变什么的工作
...where I could help people and make a difference.
现在你做什么?
What do you do now?
宴会规划
I'm a party planner.
-明天见 -好
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
看谁回来了，是瑞瑞
Look who's back. It's Ray-Ray.
那是我大学的朋友梅莉莎
That was my friend, Melissa, from college.
她看起来很有意思!
She seems really, really fun!
她真的很甜，我们曾经很亲近
She's actually sweet, and we used to be very close.
等一下，她不是那个你…?
Wait a minute. She's not the one who you...?
你什么? 你什么?
Who you what? Who you what?
是 哇!
- Yes. - Wow!
哇，什么? 你什么?
Wow, what? Who you what?
没什么大不了
Oh, it's not a big deal.
他们是情人
They were lovers.
什么? 什么?
- What? - What?
不，我们不是情人，没有什么
No, we weren't. It was nothing.
大四的一天晚上，我们去参加舞会…
It was one night, senior year, and we went to a party...
喝了很多桑格利塔酒，你知道，结果…
...had a lot of sangria, and you know, ended up...
我们接吻了
...kissing for a bit.
我的两个老婆都是同性恋
So that's two of my wives.
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
找她回来! 罗斯，去拿桑格利塔酒!
To bring her back here! Ross, get the sangria!
Friends S07E20 瑞秋的吻
The One With Rachel's Big Kiss
这儿是乐队的所在，这儿是吧台
So this is where the band is.And here's the bar.
这些大头针上有人名，瑞秋，你在这里
And all these pins have people's names on them.Rach, here you are.
为什么不给我一杯曼哈顿…
Why don't we just put me with a Manattan in my hand...
让我和可爱的酒吧服务生聊天
...talking to the cute bartender.
这些大头针不是用来玩的，是不?
These pins aren't for playing, are they?
红的是我的客人，蓝色的是你的
The red are my guests, and the blue are yours.
真可怜，我只有10个客人
This is so sad. I only have like 10 pins.
钱德，轻松一点，这不是比赛
Chandler, relax. It's not a contest.
不是实力相近的比赛
Certainly not a close one.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
不要再想了!
Stop picturing it!
我想这样可以了 座位表好了，这是我们的婚礼
I think that's it. The seating chart is done.This is our wedding.
他们看来玩得很开心，不是吗?
They all look like they're having fun don't they?
我爸妈坐哪里?
So where are my parents gonna be?
如果这是结婚礼堂…
Well, if this is the wedding hall...
那么你的父母会在皇后区的家里
...then your parents would be over here at home in Queens.
他们没有被邀请? 不，他们一定会很伤心
They're not invited? Oh, no, they're gonna be crushed!
为什么他们以为会被邀请呢?
Why would they think they're invited?
你问倒我了，我不…
You got me. I don't...
乔伊! 我以为父母都会来
- Joey! - Look, I thought parents were coming.
你的父母会来，钱德的父母也会来
Your parents are coming. Chandler's are coming.
罗斯的父母也会来
Ross' parents are coming.
罗斯的父母就是我的父母
Ross' parents are my parents.
看，父母们都会来
Well, see, parents are coming.
-我们应该请他们 -你只是想要更多的蓝色大头针
- We should invite them.- You just want more blue pins.
这实在太惨了
Well, this is just sad.
好，也许能把他们排进来 不过要重新安排位子
All right.Maybe I can fit them in if I just do some rearranging.
瑞秋可能要坐在吧台
Rachel may have to sit at the bar.
没有问题
That is not a problem.
-也许你可以叫一杯桑格利塔酒 -去你的!
- Maybe you'll order a little sangria.- Get out of here!
这是我们的礼服 如果你有喜欢的，可以便宜些
These are our tuxedos.If you like anything, we can make a deal.
全部都可以 但这三件是莫妮卡先核准的
Anything at all.But these are the three that Monica pre-approved.
谢谢你替我们搞好关系
Thanks a lot for hooking me up.
我想请你参加我们的婚礼做我的客人
And I want you to know that I want you to attend our wedding as my guest.
我是莫妮卡的伴娘
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
别想把我变成蓝色大头针
Okay, don't try to blue-pin me.
这些不错 是不错
- Well, these look nice. - They are nice.
名人穿过这些之后，就送回来这儿
When celebrities are done with them, they send them back.
你是指像颁奖典礼之后? 有些是
- You mean like for award shows?- Some of them.
它们都上过红地毯，被人叫着：
They've been down the red carpet with people yelling:
“你穿的是谁的? 你看来棒极了!”
"Who are you wearing? You look fabulous!"
容我建议你多看一点ESPN体育台…
Might I suggest watching a little more ESPN...
少看一点娱乐节日!
...and a little less E!
谁穿过这些?
Okay. Who wore those?
-这是汤姆布若考穿过的（NBC最著名的主持人） -不错嘛
- Well, this one's Tom Brokaw. - Not bad.
这是保罗欧尼尔穿过的
This one is Paul O'Neill.
他是谁?
Who's that?
他是洋基棒球队的球员，真的，多看ESPN
He plays for the Yankees. Seriously, ESPN.
有时候，开着它当背景也好
Just once in a while. Have it on in the background.
这是皮尔斯布鲁斯南穿过的 皮尔斯布鲁斯南?
- This one was Pierce Brosnan.- Pierce Brosnan?
真的吗?
Are you serious?
007?
这是詹姆斯邦德的燕尾服? 我一定要穿詹姆斯邦德的燕尾服结婚
This is James Bond's tux?I have to get married in James Bond's tux.
很酷
It's a pretty cool tux.
不只如此，我会是英格兰最强力的武器
It's not just that.I would be England's most powerful weapon.
女王陛下的秘密特务 四处旅游的断肠人
A jet-setting heartbreaker on Her Majesty's secret service.
有着杀人执照，什么都不怕的男人
A man who fears no one, with a license to kill.
莫妮卡会不会让我穿这件?
Would Monica let me wear this?
我们应该学真正的玩法
We should really learn how to play the real way.
我喜欢我们的玩法
I like our way.
将军!
Chess!
走得好 是啊
- Nice move. - Yeah.
我替罗斯和钱德找到燕尾服 你需要吗?
I hooked Ross and Chandler up with tuxedos.Do you need one?
不，我不穿燕尾服
No, I'm not wearing a tux.
你要穿什么? 多彩的袍子
- What are you gonna wear?- Multi-colored robes.
也许戴一顶帽子
And maybe a hat.
莫妮卡知道吗? 不
- Does Monica know about this? - No.
你告诉她时我可以在场吗?
Can I please be there when you tell her?
晚上要不要去看电影?
You want to go to a movie tonight?
我要和梅莉莎吃饭
I'm having dinner with Melissa.
我可以来吗?
Can I come?
我不说话 你只会听见我的摄影机的声音
I won't talk. You'll just hear my video camera.
-什么? 怎么回事? -我可以告诉她吗?
- What? What's going on? - Can I tell her?
你要真正发生的事，还是乔伊的淫荡版本
Do you want what happened, or Joey's lewd version?
乔伊的 好
- Joey's. - Okay.
我有一个大学朋友…
I had this college friend...
我不应该告诉乔伊 有一次…
...and I made the mistake of telling Joey that one time...
她和我接吻了…
...she and I, you know, kissed a little bit.
是啊，我相信有的
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
-真的 -当然
- It did. - Sure.
真的发生了
Hey. It happened.
是大四那年，那是一次社团聚会…
It was senior year. It was after the Sigma Chi luau...
我和梅莉莎喝得大醉
...and Melissa and I got very drunk.
结果我们两个接吻了
And we ended up kissing.
好几分钟呢?
For several minutes.
表示她喝了几杯，轻轻吻在脸颊上
Which means she had a couple spritzers and a peck on the cheek.
你为什么要夺走这件事呢?
Why are you taking this away from me?
为什么这么难让你相信?
Why is it so hard for you to believe?
好吧，我不知道你是同性恋
Okay. I just didn't know that you were a lesbian.
我没说我是同性恋 我只是说那件事发生了
I'm not saying that I'm a lesbian. I'm just saying that this happened.
只是觉得很狂野，你是这么地…
It just seems pretty wild. And you're so...
乏味
...vanilla.
乏味? 我才不乏味 我做很多疯狂的事
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla. I do lots of crazy things.
我喝醉了，在拉斯维加斯结婚
I mean, I got drunk and married in Vegas.
和罗斯
To Ross.
如果你不相信我…
If you don't believe me...
今晚和我一起去吃饭 她会告诉你
...just come with me to dinner tonight and she'll tell you.
好吧，可是我想像不出来
Okay. Because I can't picture it.
你该看看我脑袋里的画面
You should get inside my head.
猜我为你的婚礼弄到什么?
Guess what I got for your wedding?
头像挂衣架，瘦巴巴的伴?
A freakishly thin date with a hanger for a head?
瑞秋替我弄到一件燕尾服 但不是随便的一件
Rachel hooked me up with a tux. But not just any tux.
是蝙蝠侠的!
Batmars tux!
什么? 没错
- What? - That's right.
为瓦尔基墨特别订做 让他穿在票房冠军电影...
Made expressly for Val Kilmer, and worn by him in the hit film...
那部他演的蝙幅侠电影里
...that Batman film he was in.
你不能穿那件，我要穿名人的燕尾服
You can't wear that. I'm wearing the famous tux.
詹姆斯邦德的燕尾服! 怎样?
- James Bond's tux! - So?
怎样? 如果你穿那件会让我的不那么特别
So? If you wear that, it'll make mine less special.
你需要用一些东西来让那天特别吗?
You need something to make this day special?
喂! 你有了最特别的一样
Hello! You have the most special thing of all.
你娶了你最爱的女人
You are marrying the woman you love.
不要抢走我的锋头，拜托?
Don't take away my cool thing. Pretty please?
“拜托”? 不怎么像007的风格
"Pretty please?" Not very 007.
如果你要结婚 我不会做任何让你生气的事
If you were getting married, I'd never do anything to upset you.
-你和我妹妹上床 -那很007
- You slept with my sister. - That was pretty 007.
好，你来了，好，我想出办法了
Okay, good, you're here. All right, I figured it out.
我把这两桌的8个人，加上你父母…
I'm gonna take 2 tables of 8, add your parents...
变成3桌6个人
...and make them into 3 tables of 6.
我已经通知了办席的人，都弄好了!
And I called the caterer. We are good to go!
他们不来了
Yeah. They're not coming.
什么?
What?
他们觉得你是因为我才邀请他们的
They think that you only invited them because of me.
他们觉得不受欢迎
They feel unwanted.
真糟糕，是真的，但真糟糕
That's too bad. It's true. But too bad.
你可以打电话给我妈
If you could just call my mom.
让她知道你希望他们去
Just let her know you want them there.
她送过你很多很多意大利面
This is a woman who has sent you many lasagnas.
不，她没有
No, she hasn't.
有些没有投送到你手里不是她的错
Is it her fault if some didn't make it to you?
我要说什么?
What am I gonna say?
告诉她请贴搞乱了，不，怪邮局好了
Tell them you mixed up invitations.No, blame it on the post office.
他们最恨邮局，还有爱尔兰人
They hate the post office. And the Irish.
不过我想你不能怪到他们头上
But I don't think you could blame it on them.
喂? 你好，崔比亚尼太太？ 我是莫妮卡盖勒
Hello? Yeah, hi. Mrs. Tribbiani? This is Monica Geller.
我想告诉你 我们很希望你们能来参加婚礼
I'm just calling to say that we really hope you can make it to the wedding.
我们很多请贴都没寄到
Apparently some of our invitations weren't delivered.
我猜又是可恶的邮局搞砸的
I guess there was some screw-up at the damn post office.
就是嘛!
Tell me about it!
什么美国邮局嘛? 更像是美国遗失局
Yeah, the U.S. Post Office?No. More like U.S. Lost Office.
他们搞什么，是爱尔兰人吗?
What are they, Irish?
他叫艾伦，我们在一起三年了
Anyway, his name's Allen.And we've been going out for three years.
他是我做宴会规划的第一位客户
He was my first client when I became a party planner.
那时他正要规划给他女朋友的宴会
He was actually planning a party for his girlfriend at the time.
嗯
Oh, well.
-他是锡拉丘兹大学“θ、β、π”社团的 -真好
- He was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse.- That's great.
你参加过社团吗? 当然
- Were you ever in a sorority? - Of course.
我是大腿大卫生棉条的成员
Yes. I was a Thigh Mega Tampon.
哪一个?
What one?
我们也很庞大，但后来被关掉了…
We were huge too. But they had to shut us down...
因为瑞吉娜佛兰姬死于酒精中毒
...when Regina Phalangie died of alcohol poisoning.
真是糟糕，一个女孩就毁了大家
Isn't it a shame when one girl ruins it for the whole bunch?
无论如何…
Anyway...
说到喝太多，我告诉菲比…
Speaking of drinking too much, I told Phoebe...
在∑Χ社烤野猪宴那晚，我们亲吻的事
...about that crazy night after the Sigma Chi luau where we made out.
什么?
What?
记得我们…我们穿着纱笼布裙 还有椰子壳比基尼上衣
Remember we... Come on, we had sarongs on and the coconut bikini tops.
之后我们回到家，在那儿疯癫…
We went back to the house and got really silly...
然后我们接吻了
...and we made out.
瑞瑞，我不知道你在说什么
Wow, Ray-Ray, I have no idea what you're talking about.
真的?
Really?
罗斯是蝙蝠侠
Ross is Batman.
他的确是把身份掩护了很久
Well, he did manage to keep his identity secret for a long time.
瑞秋替罗斯弄到瓦尔基默在蝙蝠侠里穿的那件燕尾服
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
蝙蝠侠比詹姆斯邦德酷多了
Batman is so much cooler than James Bond.
-什么? 007有很多的工具 -蝙蝠侠有工具腰带
- What? 007 has all those gadgets.- Batman has a utility belt.
-007有很酷的车 -蝙蝠侠有蝙蝠车
- 007 has a fancy car.- Batman has the Batmobile.
-007有很多女人 -蝙蝠侠有罗宾
- 007 gets all the ladies.- Batman has Robin.
我们有ESPN台，对吧?
We get ESPN, right?
你何不穿上你的007燕尾服 我替你调一杯马提尼酒
How about you go put on your 007 tuxedo, and I'll make you a martini?
我不喜欢马提尼
I don't like martinis.
-一杯摇摇饮料，用一只搞笑吸管? -好的
- A Yoo-hoo with a funny straw? - Yum.
请贴上写晚上6点
I know the invitation says 6 p. M.
是指6点入席，还是6点开始表演?
But does that mean get there at 6, or the show starts at 6?
“表演”?
"The show"?
对，婚礼，知道了
Right, the wedding. Gotcha.
不过婚礼会晚一点开始，对不?
But weddings start a little late, right?
你有参加过我规划的婚礼吗?
Have you ever been to one of my weddings?
那天我侄女受洗礼…
Well, it's the same day as my niece's christening...
我希望我父母能看到我
...and I want my parents to see me.
我的部份是在开始时 不在其他部份的表演…婚礼
My part's in the beginning.I'm not in the rest of the show... Wedding.
婚礼6点开始
The wedding starts at 6.
好，我听到了
Okay. I totally hear you.
这样如何? 我可以表演到他们到达
How about this? I vamp till they get there.
你要“表演”
You'll "vamp"?
像是把氛围搞热 问他们从哪里来
Like warm up the crowd. Ask where they're from.
因为乔伊崔比亚尼在时 你有牧师和演艺人员
Because in Joey Tribbiani, you get a minister and an entertainer.
我是一位“牧艺人”
I'm a "ministainer." All right?
没有更好的，没有更伟大的
There's no one better. There's no one greater.
拜托，天呐，不要表演
Oh, please, God. Don't vamp.
好吧，我会跟钱德说的
Okay, maybe I'll talk to Chandler.
也许他会喜欢在007点钟结婚
And maybe he'd like to get married at 007 o'clock.
好吧，再给你10分钟，就这样了
All right. I will give you 10 extra minutes.That is it.
太好了! 非常感谢
That's great! Thank you so much.
我们真走运．燕尾服很合身
Well, we're in luck. The tux fits perfectly.
钱德，那件外套你穿太大了
Chandler, that jacket, it's way too big.
没事．裤子太短了
Oh, that's okay. The pants are way too small.
对不起，甜心．你不能穿那些衣服
I'm sorry, sweetie. You cannot wear that.
这就意味着只有罗斯是最酷的那个
Now this means Ross is gonna be the only cool one.
对了，我从未想过我会说这样的话
Something, by the way, I never thought I would say.
兄弟，脱掉吧，你就像个傻子
Dude, take that thing off. You look like a fool.
到隔壁去 我给你看看一些牧师的头饰
Come next door. I got some minister headdresses I want you to see.
你怎么能不记得我们接吻的事?
How can you not remember us kissing?
我不知道，我不记得那些从没发生过的事
I don't know. I don't remember a lot of things that never happened.
记得我们在睡觉的廊子时一直笑 一直笑?
Remember, we were on the sleeping porch? We couldn't stop giggling.
我们的椰子壳撞在一起
Our coconuts kept knocking together.
乔伊的头在某处爆炸了
Somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
我不想让你不舒服…
I don't want to make you uncomfortable...
但我告诉菲比这件事发生过，她不相信我
...but I told Phoebe it happened, and she doesn't believe me.
对不起，如果我认为它发生了，我会承认的
I'm sorry. I mean, if I thought it happened, I would say it.
也许我昏过去了 你在我睡觉时对我做了什么？
Maybe I passed out and you did stuff to me while I was sleeping.
没有!
No!
好了 好吧，没事
- All right. - Okay, fine.
你不用承认，因为我知道发生过
You don't have to admit it because I know that it happened.
好!
Okay!
你必须承认! 我们亲嘴了! 说!
You have to admit it! We kissed! Say it!
没关系，你不必这么做，我相信你
It's okay, you don't have to do this. I believe you.
如果你说你吻了梅莉莎 那么你就吻了梅莉莎
If you say you kissed Melissa, then you kissed Melissa.
谢谢，菲比 好
- Thank you, Phoebe. - Okay.
-可是她没有 -我知道
- But she didn't. - I know.
你带着它走来走去?
You carry that around?
是的，我发现它是个好话题
Yes. I find it to be something of a conversation piece.
-你和…? -甘瑟
- Between you and...? - Gunther.
我们何不穿上?
Why don't we put them on?
拍张蝙蝠侠和詹姆斯邦德一起的照片
Get a picture of Batman and James Bond, together.
我很愿意，但我的裤子小了一点
I would, but my pants are a little tight.
小了一点? 我可以看到里面的两个0和一个7
A little tight? I could see 00 and 7 in those things.
真糟糕
Well, that stinks.
我很期待一起穿我们的名人燕尾服呢
I was looking forward to wearing our celebrity tuxes together.
-你不穿你的了? -你开玩笑? 是蝙蝠侠的燕尾服
- So you're not gonna be wearing yours?- Are you kidding? It's Batmars tux!
我试穿看看
Let me try it on.
好，只能穿上衣，两个0和一个7不要进去
Okay. But just the jacket. 00 and 7 are not getting in there.
双面通风的舒适，蝙蝠侠!
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman!
这是什么?
What's this?
《真情难舍》首映请贴?
An invitation to the At First Sight premiere?
瓦尔基墨没有在《蝙蝠侠》里穿这件
Val Kilmer didn't wear this in Batman.
他穿这件去参加他演瞎子的那部文艺爱情片首映
He wore it to the premiere of a fruity love story where he was a blind guy.
给我看
Let me see that.
老天
Oh, man.
你唯一的超能力是稍微强化的嗅觉
The only super power you have is the slightly heightened sense of smell.
可以和你们谈谈吗?
Can I talk to you guys for a second?
我放弃了，你要怎样就怎样吧
I give up. Whatever you want, you can have it.
你要唱歌还是跳舞?
You want to sing a song or do a dance?
还是要你妈在圣坛前尖叫种族歧视的字眼? 我都不在乎
You want your mom at the altar screaming racial slurs?I don't care.
我只是要谢谢你们为我父母做的一切
I just want to thank you guys for what you did for my parents.
他们很高兴能参加你们特别的一天
They're so happy to be a part of your special day.
告诉他们我们很高兴他们会来
Tell them we're glad they're coming.
我会的，看看他们替我准备参加婚礼的衣服!
I will. Oh, check out what they got me to wear for the ceremony!
我替你们证婚时这样穿，然后…
I wear it like this when I marry you guys.And then this...
在宴会时这样穿
...is for party time.
它发生了，我告诉你它发生了
It happened. I am telling you it happened.
很高兴认识你
It was great meeting you.
瑞秋? 我想我不会给你打电话了，因为…
And, Rachel? I don't think I'll be calling you because...
你变得好奇怪
...you know, you've gotten weird.
保重，两位
Take care, you guys.
等一下，好，听着
Wait a minute. Okay, look.
那天晚上是我所做过最狂野的一件事
That night was the one wild thing I've ever done in my life.
我不会让你夺去它
I won't let you take it away.
如果你不记得那件事 也许你会记得这个…
So if you don't remember that, maybe you'll remember this...
我的天，你爱我
Oh, my God. You love me.
什么?
What?
我当然记得，这些日子里我一直想着它
Of course I remember. I think about it all the time.
我还能听到椰子壳碰在一起的声音…
I can still hear the coconuts knocking together...
我不想告诉你 因为我不觉得你会回应我的爱
I didn't want to tell you, because I didn't think you'd return my love...
看是谁突然变得害羞
Look who's being suddenly shy.
你一定和我一样感觉
You have to feel what I feel.
没人能不是真心而吻得那么好
Nobody can kiss that good and not mean it.
我只是吻功很好
I'm just a good kisser.
闭嘴
Shut up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你不必抱歉
You don't have to be sorry.
我在开玩笑
I'm obviously kidding.
我没爱上你，我没爱上她
I'm not in love with you. I'm not in love with her.
我没听到椰子壳撞在一起
I don't hear coconuts banging together.
我和男友做爱时没幻想你的脸
I don't picture your face when I make love to my boyfriend.
我要走了
Anyway, I gotta go.
吻别好吗?
A kiss goodbye?
不要? 好吧
No? Okay.
我不知道那会…
I mean, I had no idea that that would...
这是怎么回事?
What the hell was that?
想看看这一场混乱是怎么样的
Just wanted to see what all the fuss was about.
-然后呢? -我有过更好的
- And? - I've had better.
我找到一件合身的
I found one that fits.
是啊，人们常说 第23次是最好的一次
Well, you know what they say?23rd time's a charm.
看看你，好英俊
Look at you, all handsome.
-是谁穿过的? -有关系吗?
- Whose is it? - Does it matter?
唯一重要的是你看来很英俊
All that matters is that you look so handsome.
-是谁的? -我不想说
- Whose is it? - I don't want to say.
拜托，我没事的，是谁的?
Come on, I don't care. Whose is it?
黛安基顿（70年代知性女星）
Diane Keaton.